good morning it is 8:30 so I'm here and
I'm live and I don't know what today's
gonna be coz I figured things out like
everybody else and today is a lower than
I have been during these times day like
just uh downloading information figuring
things out and in that mode its heart
it's I'm figuring it out in my language
in my head so it's harder to communicate
that to the world than things that I
have more concretely figured out or I
feel I have more concretely figure it
out but this that we are safe enough to
try and then directly after writing that
title there's this for innovation in
society it comes from having safety
being safe enough to try and also being
desperate enough to need it and right
now we are both of those things I am
both of those things
this constant desperation for the world
to need to be better different and I it
is safe enough to do what I am doing I
am NOT putting my money on the line it's
only my favorite limited spoons but
doing this is energy positive I wasn't
doing it I would be in a much worse day
than doing it because it feeds back in
more energy than it takes to fight your
on this planet but that is again back to
like the desperation that because of my
desperation to need to find energy
everywhere to need to create a easy
simple life for my needs for my
desperation
it became safe enough to try and as a
society before what is currently
happening seeing the world as a
desperate yet unaware of its
desperateness I had to come to create
something that was safe enough to try
something we could scaffold under the
current existing economy to create
something that isn't fragile and has the
capacity for everyone to give what they
have to give in a way that they want to
give it and live their version of an
amazing life in return it's the basics
that is something that allows for safe
enough to try from that space that right
now under the economy the one that is in
trouble a lot of it is there because of
safe enough to try and desperate and
desperate at the same time they're both
they're both there and that is it's
finding that balance in each of us
because we a lot of times dictate the
desperation that you're not going to be
accepted you're not going to be loved
you're not gonna be deemed worthy if
you're not wearing these clothes driving
this car have this profession at least
be able to provide for your family at
to be able to make a relationship work
at least be able to cook food from
scratch whereas you love Red John the
pandemic but there's this desperation
that comes from needing to live up to
society's standards in not just one area
but every single area of life and there
are ones that come easy to us and ones
that are difficult and they're different
for all of us and that enforced
desperation doesn't allow for a space of
safe enough to try right now we have
still some time on our hands we have the
new for some of us knowledge of our
systems not being in what we thought
they were that our governments don't
have the answers for that they do think
that they actually can function in some
way collectively to be able to do things
that are safe enough to try and I don't
know that's taking up the economy with
safe don't try because they don't they
don't have answers they don't know the
interconnectedness of it and that we
need we need the solutions we need to be
able to come to we need what is safe
enough to try and we are at the point of
desperate enough that we can't fail that
like we need to figure something out
something that helps us trust a system
of information something that helps us
come come out of extreme poverty like
that each of us is that fragile that we
can't keep a roof over our head or food
on the table if somebody else isn't
employing us and even if we're the
entrepreneur and the person employing
other people that can collapse as well
like oh but if we can't go outside if
something shifts we can't
our economy isn't as yeah I guess I am I
didn't know you were here until you
spoke what sized a little one guy with
one thing in the corner but my water go
but today is a I want to say low because
it's not like it's judged as less than
just uh introspective day or morning say
Thursday yesterday was Wednesday and I
like missed my Omega Group just forgot
about it I was trying to track down
these LPS for my kid but I went to pick
up we went on the porch everything was
just like a little more energy some of
the less energy this today which is how
it is that is again as I was saying
before like my desperation leads to
innovation to create a world that is
safe enough to actually innovate in
balance the balance between safety and
desperation and I'm just basically
sitting and talking nope itself but
you're welcome
oh no I am only talking about person on
youtube and periscope and there's one
person total cuz it adds them up for me
that is what is currently going on I do
this every morning at 8:30 there's some
of the days of the week that have more
not more viewers or participation but
this is what I'm supposed to be doing so
my butt is in the seat and I'm pressing
record and right before this I got very
much that like this is the point the
point is to share the journey not to
have a video that is about other people
joining in and gaining who wants to gain
viewership have even it's about
showcasing the actual journey which is
there are low days where like and I've
got anything planned that you guys
there are days with our more viewers and
there's days where people call in our
Colin's number on the screen on YouTube
in the description there is a link to
the stream yard to come on and be on
camera as well and that would be helpful
because this I might my brain might
click in and be able to have a
conversation that's like a second cup of
coffee but I can't until this is over
now
now that I've thought about that it's a
lot of work making a coffee well on
camera
hmm but this different this I was
watching what was I just watching ELISA
what can I picture her last name yay
he'll a Riesling just like a journalist
it's not like a journalist she is a
journalist I think you started out with
no problem
and it was from the American Dream
collapsing that it was from the 2008
financial crisis followed in like 2011
2012 like we just have the same problems
that are because we are disconnected
because you have this like tiny group of
the economy of the population going
through something they're desperate
but their desperation like when you're
too desperate
you can't innovate because you need to
eat like you need to take anything do
anything you don't feel safe enough to
innovate and my guess is some of us need
more safety and it makes some of us need
more of the desperation to innovate but
if you're too desperate you can't I
don't know if you can be too safe it
doesn't seem to be a level like theirs
if we're dictating it for ourselves how
safe do we want it to be how easy to
leave want it to be or need it to be the
problem is putting that on the other
people it's like this is
the median lighter
it gave me people brain Oh
one of these days I don't know what what
what one of these days nothing
absolutely nothing one of these days
that I'm just posed to sit here and
allow it to unfold both on this
broadcast you're welcome
and in life in general that it comes as
it's supposed to but what I am here to
help create like I'm more interested in
the safety side than the desperation
sight to create for other people because
there I mean I need more safety to be
able to innovate but then it comes from
like the desperation that I have in my
life is not really like invoked by
somebody else
it's by physical neurological emotional
limitations but I try to argue with but
they don't really they're not really
arguable versus the desperation of the
economic systems and stuff that like
we're doing and we're creating says I
mean what
happens too but you don't have like a
lot of what I don't have power over
necessarily in and creates desperation
in the bigger world is the stuff but
then I met I'm supposed to feel bad
about in the interior world part for not
controlling right your diet your
exercise your mental state your a lot of
what that like manufactured desperation
I don't not make any sense primal is
nice
some are we working it out and
exploiting it someone else she just
happens to be what I am doing today at
8:30 in the morning hmm
do you not necessarily get to yawn for
an hour I could probably stand for half
an hour how does anyone else had just
that's the kind of thing I want to know
and have access to the data like how
many people are feel that they are at
their best to innovate whatever the
renovation is whether it's creativity or
inventing something when they were
desperate and when they're safe and what
that balance is how desperate how safe
they need to be in order to operate at
their highest self because there is that
I was getting from me Lisa lightning
thing why can't I remember name words
are not in my brain it's like a it's
like there's literally a word a letter
missing from the last name in my head
thanks Adam
I love taking l I think it's Lisa way
not the point
but what's the point does written said
how many people of what's that balance
for them how desperate they need to be
to innovate like when have they what has
that desperation looked like to them
because there's people who are desperate
enough to come up with two funds to to
fundraise come for the mass amount of
money or to become the researchers
themselves when they're like kid has a
rare disorder and oh and there are
people who are not right it doesn't mean
you love your kid any less it doesn't
mean that you aren't like sometimes even
in your same desperation that you might
lose your kid or your kid might not have
a high quality of life your your safety
changes right if what you still need to
do is go to work so that you have health
care so that you can provide the health
care for your child your that's gonna be
your focus rather than the bakery
surgeon and all that stuff so like
there's again a balance that you have to
be safe enough to get to be desperate
enough and you have to not be desperate
enough in order to get to be safe enough
to innovate and so it's that and I think
it is it's different in each of us like
I said well because for our
circumstances in our lives and just who
we are as people how much about were
capable of dealing with safe enough to
try there's this saying though in the
community of it being safe enough to try
that when somebody has an idea they put
it forth to the community and that is
often the response like it's safe enough
to try let's try it let's see if it
works well someone finds a fatal flaw in
the plan it's safe enough to try and
what I am maybe suggesting is and what
it was kind of coming through before
this what is safe enough to try is
creating a world that's safe enough to
try like creating a world where everyone
has basic
abundance so you have food shelter
clothing connection education what that
bottom base looks like is up to us what
do we want if we're there what do we
want to point out there if it kind of
needs a democracy the most of the
bottoms like the thud vast numbers are
on the side of the vast numbers and we
can basically do anything and everything
when we truly come together and create
the system that is safe enough to try
for all of us and so it only needs to be
in a room an improvement on what we're
doing and none that's be safe enough to
try and that is partly for every
different because we are also desperate
enough like we have both sides of it
simultaneously the people right now in
Canada in America in Australia and
Europe I'm probably forgetting a lot of
other countries there are wealthy enough
then it's safe enough to try things like
using Universal ways I can do it safe
enough I don't know if it's safe enough
to try rent freezes it's made but it's
also not safe enough to not try it like
it's all right to take your economy have
massive inflation because we can't just
pause the economy for three months say
okay nothing's too there's no besides
buying food and the basic necessities
there is no rent due there is no
interest to on things no principal and
interest you on payments and so it
doesn't need to ripple up and then
figure out where there's the broken
pieces stuff the other things fall
through the cracks select companies and
pieces of our economy to fall through
the cracks
so like as a society right now it's safe
enough to try creating something
different that doesn't need to be
universal that doesn't need to be hey
everyone stay inside right we're already
dealing with that in every different
country and different locality is going
to be having a different way now both do
this I mean not everyone was inside
different places have tried different
things and then coming out of it we're
gonna try different things I don't be
able to see what worked the best and
what did not work the best for the best
about datas capability but as we are
still inside and coming back and people
are waking up to the cracks that are in
society it's like what what isn't safe
enough to try it's just let it continue
as it is that it's not safe enough to
drive but creating our individual lives
so they're safe enough to try even other
governments don't give us UVI we know
that we're fed clothed sheltered without
needing them to give it to us then we
are able to come up with solutions
because our lives are safe enough that
we can we can innovate and create and
the like the world right now is
desperate enough and those of us that
are aware of that are desperate enough
that and more and more people are waking
up to that desperation that they like
feed into each other as well your
desperation and the safety of innovation
mm oh well I can stay on for like five
more minutes almost my brain kicks into
high gear here
yeah somebody wants call him there is a
link in the description on YouTube oh oh
how did write this down before I came on
that's a cool one since that's the thing
if I get that I really have tomorrow
we're doing coaching life's purpose and
period purpose which might be the last
one I do that's the last one that's
pertinent to the five questions but I
guess no it is part of the five
questions the other piece of the journey
and then Saturday I do the f-d-a update
on my five question journey that a lot
of what I'm figuring out what my journey
is what I'm sharing with people is me
figuring out what it is I have to give
and what it is I need to be able to give
that and those are both also partner
five questions that what one of them is
like who are who am i who are my people
I mean answering those as part of what I
need but also one of the question is
literally what do I need and that's what
we're answering next Tuesday
yeah I can't even follow a sequence of a
story to be able to share it so that's
probably not gonna happen oh I could
charge my way through it uh was it don't
think it was yesterday no because
yesterday was the solution raising
Tuesday maybe I had done one of these on
I just watched a youtube video every so
often someone will comment on an old one
already watch it and yeah well no
offense bring that person who commented
on it so I found it came on the idea
cafe for this loot no I Jade cafe was
Tuesday and he also sent a want to say
quiz that's not right at all like
personality traits to find out what
questions you your personality asks and
what that means about you which is
interesting and I think I just
trusty but um he offered to connect
those of us who wanted to with that
resource and so yes but I've yet to take
that personality quiz so if y'all do
that right after but I don't know if I
should do it in the current state or
maybe my current stay it's the perfect
one we'll see but it's just cool like
how he he found it jumped on the idea
cafe and getting that resource which is
a resource under the umbrella of at
least in my brain under that node of Who
am I knowing what questions I asked
knowing what the personality traits the
one I can never remember the intps one
that everyone seems to remember what
they are and I can never remember what I
am and also knowing that in taking that
test if it I had a book here there we go
was over there uh-huh whenever I take a
quiz and one of the options is to be a
combination of the traits
I am the combination of the trades I
read this book which is why it was
wasn't quite as random as in a few uh
which is also because like my sister I
was like how many of the books on my
shelf were there because my sister it's
like this that will change your life
this one actually was interesting about
our personal attachment styles and most
people are either securely attached it's
like supposedly 50% of the population I
do not know where those people are I
don't even know what that feel like or
avoidant or the opposite of avoidant
find the table of contents anxious and
avoidant and secure and so some people
are anxious attachment simple avoidant
attachment and some people are
combination of mine wasn't even new
combination of just those two it was a
combination of all three it's like yeah
I can see how I'm like uniquely
dysfunctional because I also have the
secure attachment style at least a
little bit so it plays it the other ones
but that's like a common theme in my
life that like
you can be the multiple of the two
things if it's a binary or in this case
a multiple the three things so I'm
interested in taking those tests and
even in the int PF thing whenever I take
it there are two traits that are so
close to the 50% the faces like will
swing from like 48 to 52 in either
direction so I am both of them okay but
they're quite I don't know and I'm like
that with with a lot of things which is
why I am so curious though Who am I
question to know myself for means to
kind of understand the different pieces
and not I don't know where unique do I
really need to take quizzes to know who
I am yes I do I like it I enjoy it you
know if you don't if you don't that's
hoping this would be a much better
broadcast but yeah we come on me in my
brain at 8:30 in the morning every day
in some days there's fog so you drove up
somewhere yesterday this is the wealth
I'm working in but even in that like I
mean getting the desperation innovation
thing out of that it's still pretty
awesome if I focused on the fact it
can't you can't tell a story and can't
remember it again that
innovation comes from both desperation
and safety finding the figuri note so I
think what my brains we got even through
this whole time
but the solution raisins are both safe
enough to try as me as an individual but
also a society that finding 10,000
people each putting in $10 and creating
something that is safe enough to try in
that domain in education and
transportation and wonderful in the
meadow and aslam interested in energy
the one we're doing this coming week on
Wednesday
partly because yes we are desperate
enough let the world is desperate enough
individually we're desperate enough and
that we see how closer to starvation and
collapse we are then maybe originally
thought a few months ago by most people
I'm getting back to the other thing
solution raising is safe enough to drive
thanks I'll oh it's not it's not really
a bad that's why I'm like it's low like
my energy is low my brainpower is like
on plug-in low battery but I know that
like different things come out of it so
it's just writing it no problem well if
you're like rap oh this is the problem
because I unlike reading comments none
of you know what I'm talking about
I love said this on youtube and also
Raymond slepen slept in this morning so
we did not have that conversation which
is probably good it's like the universe
looking after me because I'd rather have
that conversation on Monday when maybe
my brain fog is lifted and different and
then my success is you said this and I
can't even read it
although I did but I can't read it out
loud that last night part of the reason
probably Raymond missed this morning was
that I didn't he brought back last night
when I said to the link but I was not in
a states actually like even hit the
thumbs up button just like yes I will
see you at 7:00 morning and then we did
not we didn't want to each other so in
the morning
it's like um my birthday this year I had
something planned but I will not say
it's probably already centered on
several videos but it fell through but
part of it falling through was that like
this Airbnb wasn't able to be we weren't
able to get into it so I needed foreign
spy
brothers place with him and was just the
two of us the other person wasn't there
which means I have $100 Airbnb credit
which it was better more enticing in a
world free co-indictee like where are we
going now where am I gonna start stainer
bb-but it was actually perfect but it it
fell through it I feel like today is one
of those see me one of those days as
well
that mid Sun it was supposed to fall
through rain need like 15 cups of coffee
coffee does not my brain I don't why I
said that but I know what it's like to
have a brain that functions 80% and
sometimes have a brain that functions
you know closer to 20 30 % and there are
people out there who have brains that
function you're 30 percent never know
what it's like to have brains of
function you're 90 percent of people who
are the opposite have brains in here
they always focus in a function in
ninety to a hundred percent and don't
know what it's like at all to have
brains that function 15 to 20 percent I
do because I've experienced them both in
my life and both in a week a day it's
interesting I don't know if my brain
will focus later yesterday
I was looking forward to make a
conversation of all day noon I was like
it happens in an hour and then I was
focused on getting meself
yes and just three o'clock and I was
like oh my god I missed it cuz that's
what it ends it's about four one two
three
today's is also at one so I hope I can
stick it in my brain this one's more
functional though this one's like
admin's of gay be discussing things
which is so much less fun than my Omega
group love pick every time I don't I
I've been low I've been states like this
sat there for two hours having a
conversation and come out in a
completely different state like it's
generative rejuvenating things fall
apart when they're meant to and today
like that was part of me just showcasing
the journey it's like this is what it is
this is it's not all snow most other
people are good like why would you go
live during a state like this cuz that's
part of having the set our is that it
truly is what shows up in that hour and
rarely am I in this is why I first set
it to be 6:30 and this is a good normal
state for me at 6:30 so this is not
normal for me at 9:00 in the morning I
usually have a few hours of learning
where my brain is much more okay slide
14 scheduled in the morning for it's the
other tack good idea cafes it's all of
it but it's not because I bought it
clearly like gives my best brain power
to my purpose what I'm here to do and I
want to get my most like Harvey to
passion and like spoons for connection
and it was my kid was the language I
like him well and it's just that it's
like I can't communicate with the
outside world as easily as in other
times and so knowing that knowing that
it there this is the irony when it
wouldn't like I my other day is when
it's it's okay the people it's not great
it's not stellar but compared to the
less good times it's better and it's my
best so it's good
like when my brain can't pull a word
that's okay I work with it because my
other option is this like word salad you
make it into whatever you want it to be
oh and I said I'd say on for half an
hour and I'm 36 and so I'm gonna go and
rest my brain if my brain is in a proper
state later I might do a one-off video
to explain this concept in succinct way
which is something that came up in the
last few days was meeting especially
with all these videos they're just like
a new 30 videos that are now or like I
know about per month having a playlist
of short videos the two minutes to
five-minute ish videos under 10 minutes
for sure on the different concepts that
I want to be able to link to it like
purpose versus profit and safety versus
desperation how do you present are you
cuz this is more about me sharing my
journey of you had survived back
questions right now your brain bug
that's fun to be and yeah riding with it
it'll be better
alright well later surrender imbalance
telomere to do just learn that for
myself and that journey but in so doing
we get a create a world that works for
everybody or so I've been promised kind
of that really no I haven't in any way
have I I have with like my knowledge of
what is possible and how we get there
and that it is unfolding and work and
moving towards that I can see it but
it's like at the end and I don't know
picture a movie were no the Legos aren't
going to come out properly in any way
they promise
or they think they've been promised
something then later on it's like the
languages has been tweaked I cannot
think of an example at the moment it
would not be word solid but that but
like I have a suit like right but this
happens right because it is getting
closer to it I do have that vision it's
getting closer but the guides themselves
they're like you don't even know what's
in store like you don't even know what's
coming
guess who does they do I did I mean I
think we do have more knowledge before
we get here and we're here live in the
life under the veil knowing what were
and that is like as much as I can't
always do it I surrender to the fact
that I know what I'm meant to know when
I meant to know it so pride and Fox that
I got no even though I also there's
definitely part of me that's struggling
the brain father could be like don't
have brain fog
you're on you can't be brain fog you
need oh we gonna do it hang out the
seven-year-old as like a brain fog tap
maybe ten year old I don't know part
some you're probably four parts need ten
parts me read II never juice out and set
an alarm for the one p.m. call try to
contact them if just this is this is
part of the reason I can do video and
not write a blog consistently is that
like it's harder to write out comments
so this is like the easiest format is
conversation this is not quite a
conversation because it's one way to
myself and then reading and so that
takes different brain power there's the
point that that yep feel like
oh we're gonna smoke pot till at least
noon but I feel pretty I don't even know
does that mean none or does that mean
now one or the other
maybe there's something waiting in that
and I don't even know if I'm supposed to
go off or stay on for 20 minutes and if
I stay on
just everybody procrastinating for going
off or does it really matter I surrender
to what is like whenever it needs me to
do something I was watching
oh is that personality quiz I'm gonna go
take a personality quiz I'm not gonna do
any brain found something that it wants
to do if I can read and answer why am I
take you know yes yeah I'm going to okay
see I'm so decisive take care I will see
you tomorrow life coaching my brain what
if my brains in this stand I will not be
doing that and we're gonna be going
through what is our life's purpose and
our period purpose which has a lot to do
with our values we weren't given as
children and there is a link in the
description on the YouTube channel for
the one that says I think it says
coaching not light go change
you throw a life in front of it just
this whole connotation coaching autumn
it says life work recipe repurpose and
in there is a link to the Google Docs or
the sheets with the values on it the one
that's the kit that's used every week
and then the other one that's just for
this week nice purpose purpose
and I will see you tomorrow I wanna say
with a functioning brain which whatever
brain shows up on that at that time but
mostly during this time its functioning
so let's assume you folks